(this.webpackJsonpforms=this.webpackJsonpforms||[]).push([[0],{71:function(t,e,o){},72:function(t,e,o){},73:function(t,e,o){},82:function(t,e,o){"use strict";o.r(e);var n=o(0),i=o.n(n),a=o(25),s=o.n(a),r=(o(71),o.p,o(72),[{question:"1.     How many different positions can you set for drop cap ?",option1:"a)   1",option2:"b)   2",option3:"c)   4",option4:"d)   6",answer:"b)   2"},{question:"2.     How many ways you can save a document ?",option1:"a)   3",option2:"b)   4",option3:"c)   5",option4:"d)   6",answer:"a)   3"},{question:"3.     Single spacing in MS Word document causes - point line spacing ?",option1:"a)   10",option2:"b)   12",option3:"c)   14",option4:"d)   16",answer:"b)   12"},{question:"4.     What is the default number of lines to drop for drop cap ?",option1:"a)   3",option2:"b)   10",option3:"c)   15",option4:"d)   20",answer:"a)   3"},{question:"5.     What is the maximum number of lines you can set for a drop cap ?",option1:"a)   3",option2:"b)   10",option3:"c)   15",option4:"d)   20",answer:"b)   10"},{question:"6.     How many column can you insert in a word document in maximum ?",option1:"a)   35",option2:"b)   45",option3:"c)   55",option4:"d)   65",answer:"b)   45"},{question:"7.     In a document, What is the maximum number of columns that can be inserted in MS-Word Table ?",option1:"a)   35",option2:"b)   15",option3:"c)   63",option4:"d)   65",answer:"c)   63"},{question:"8.     What is the maximum scale percentage available in scale drop down box ?",option1:"a)   500",option2:"b)   200",option3:"c)   100",option4:"d)   90",answer:"b)   200"},{question:"9.     What is the maximum font size you can apply for any character ?",option1:"a)   163",option2:"b)   1638",option3:"c)   16038",option4:"d)   None of these",answer:"b)   1638"},{question:"10.     Word by default, places a tab step at every_mark on the ruler ?",option1:'a)   2.5"',option2:'b)   .5"',option3:'c)   .75"',option4:'d)   .1"',answer:'b)   .5"'},{question:"11.     What is the default file extension for all word documents ?",option1:"a)   txt",option2:"b)   word",option3:"c)   docs",option4:"d)   docx",answer:"d)   docx"},{question:"12.     The file type_indicates the file is a word document ?",option1:"a)   .msw",option2:"b)   .wor",option3:"c)   .wrd",option4:"d)   .doc",answer:"d)   .doc"},{question:"13.     How much space in minimum must be provided between columns ?",option1:'a)   0"',option2:'b)   0.5"',option3:'c)   1"',option4:'d)   1.5"',answer:'a)   0"'},{question:"14.     What is the smallest width of column ?",option1:'a)   0"',option2:'b)   0.5"',option3:'c)   1"',option4:'d)   1.5"',answer:'d)   1.5"'},{question:"15.     By default, your document print with ?",option1:"a)   1 inch top and bottom margins",option2:"b)   A portrait orientation",option3:"c)   1.25 inches left and right margins",option4:"d)   All of the above",answer:"b)   A portrait orientation"},{question:"16.     Word is present to use standard 8.5 by 11 inch paper with_margins ?",option1:"a)   1 inch left, right, top and bottom",option2:"b)   1.25 inch left, right top and bottom",option3:"c)   1.25 inch left and right margins and depend button",option4:"d)   1 inch left and right margins and 1.25 inch top and bottom",answer:"c)   1.25 inch left and right margins and depend button"},{question:"17.     What is the default left margin in word 2003 document ?",option1:'a)   1"',option2:'b)   1.25"',option3:'c)   1.5"',option4:'d)   2"',answer:'b)   1.25"(31.7mm)'},{question:"18.     What is the smallest and largest font size available in font size tool on formatting toolbar ?",option1:"a)   8 and 72",option2:"b)   8 and 64",option3:"c)   12 and 72",option4:"d)   None of above",answer:"a)   8 and 72"},{question:"19.     What is the default font size of a new word document based on normal template in word 2003 ?",option1:"a)   10pt",option2:"b)   12pt",option3:"c)   14pt",option4:"d)   None of above",answer:"b)   12pt"},{question:"20.     The minimum number of rows and columns in MS-Word document is ?",option1:"a)   1 and 1",option2:"b)   2 and 1",option3:"c)   2 and 2",option4:"d)   None of above",answer:"a)   1 and 1"},{question:"21.     In mail merge operation which of the following might represent the main document ?",option1:"a)   A scale brochure",option2:"b)   A form letter",option3:"c)   A database of Names and Addresses",option4:"d)   None of above",answer:"a)   A scale brochure"},{question:"22.     Pressing F8 key for three times select ?",option1:"a)   A word",option2:"b)   A sentense",option3:"c)   A paragraph",option4:"d)   entire document",answer:"b)   A sentense"},{question:"22.     What do you call a collection of character and paragraph formatting commands ?",option1:"a)   A style",option2:"b)   A template",option3:"c)   A style",option4:"d)   A boilerplate",answer:"a)   A style"},{question:"23.     What is document outline view ?",option1:"a)   A preview in a full screen",option2:"b)   A preview with margins",option3:"c)   A view with a margins and gutter",option4:"d)   A view with a structure of heading at various levels",answer:"d)   A view with a structure of heading of various levels"},{question:"24.     Ctrl+Z ?",option1:"a)   Undo the last action",option2:"b)   Redo the last action",option3:"c)   Add the new page",option4:"d)   Paste the contents clipboard",answer:"a)   Undo the last action"},{question:"25.     The ____ in the resume wizard dialog box indicates the wizard is ready to create the document ?",option1:"a)   Start panel",option2:"b)   Address panel",option3:"c)   Add/Sort Heading panel",option4:"d)   Finish panel",answer:"d)   Finish panel"},{question:"26.     What does Ctrl + = key effect ?",option1:"a)   Superscript",option2:"b)   Subscript",option3:"c)   All caps",option4:"d)   Shadow",answer:"b)   Subscript"},{question:"27.     The word wrap feature ?",option1:"a)   Automatically move text to the next line when necessary",option2:"b)   Appears at the bottom of the document",option3:"c)   All you to type over text",option4:"d)   It is the short horizontal line",answer:"a)   Automatically move text to the next line when necessary"},{question:"28.     How can you make the selected character superscriptd ?",option1:"a)   Ctrl + =",option2:"b)   Ctrl + Shift + =",option3:"c)   Alt + Ctrl + shift + =",option4:"d)   None of Above",answer:"b)   Ctrl + Shift + ="},{question:"29.     When typing in a word field manually, what must you press to insert the code's braces ?",option1:"a)   Ctrl + F6",option2:"b)   Ctrl + F9",option3:"c)   Alt + F9",option4:"d)   Shift + F12",answer:"b)   Ctrl + F9"},{question:"30.     What is the shortcut key to open the open dialog box ?",option1:"a)   F12",option2:"b)   Shift + F12",option3:"c)   Alt + F12",option4:"d)   Ctrl + F12",answer:"d)   Ctrl + F12"},{question:"31.     What is the shortcut key to split a table ?",option1:"a)   Ctrl + Alt + Enter",option2:"b)   Ctrl + Shift + Enter",option3:"c)   Alt + Shift + Enter",option4:"d)   Alt + Space + Enter",answer:"b)   Ctrl + Shift + Enter"}]),c=o(66),p=o(7),d=o(14),l=o(18),h=o(23),u=o(24),m=(o(73),o(63)),b=o(1),j=function(t){Object(h.a)(o,t);var e=Object(u.a)(o);function o(){var t;return Object(d.a)(this,o),(t=e.call(this)).state={},t}return Object(l.a)(o,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(b.jsxs)("div",{className:"App",children:[Object(b.jsx)("span",{className:"link",children:Object(b.jsx)("a",{href:"/computersquiz",children:"Home"})}),Object(b.jsxs)("marquee",{className:"intro",children:["Powered by ",Object(b.jsx)("spam",{id:"vinay",children:"Vinay Rana"})," & ",Object(b.jsx)("spam",{id:"amit",children:"Amit kumar"}),"..."]}),Object(b.jsx)("h1",{"text-align":"center",children:Object(b.jsx)("u",{children:Object(b.jsx)("i",{children:Object(b.jsx)("b",{children:"Computer MS Word MCQ Questions"})})})}),r.map((function(t,e){return Object(b.jsxs)("div",{className:"Questions",children:[Object(b.jsx)("strong",{children:Object(b.jsx)("p",{children:t.question},e)}),Object(b.jsx)("p",{children:t.option1},e),Object(b.jsx)("p",{children:t.option2},e),Object(b.jsx)("p",{children:t.option3},e),Object(b.jsx)("p",{children:t.option4},e),Object(b.jsxs)("strong",{children:["Ans : ",Object(b.jsx)("p",{className:"answer",children:t.answer},e)]}),Object(b.jsx)("hr",{})]})}))]})}}]),o}(m.Component),f=o(60),w=o(65),x=o(64),O=o(48),g=o(47),y=o(22);o(75);var q=function(){return Object(b.jsx)(g.a,{bg:"primary",expand:"lg",children:Object(b.jsxs)(w.a,{fluid:!0,children:[Object(b.jsx)(g.a.Brand,{href:"#",children:"Computer Study"}),Object(b.jsx)(g.a.Toggle,{"aria-controls":"navbarScroll"}),Object(b.jsxs)(g.a.Collapse,{id:"navbarScroll",children:[Object(b.jsxs)(O.a,{className:"me-auto my-2 my-lg-0",style:{maxHeight:"100px"},navbarScroll:!0,children:[Object(b.jsx)(O.a.Link,{href:"#action1",children:"signup"}),Object(b.jsx)(O.a.Link,{href:"#action2",children:"login"}),Object(b.jsxs)(y.a,{title:"MCQ",id:"navbarScrollingDropdown",className:"homelink",children:[Object(b.jsx)(y.a.Item,{href:"/computersquiz/msword",className:"link",children:"MS Word"}),Object(b.jsx)(y.a.Item,{href:"/computersquiz/msword",className:"link",children:"MS Excel"}),Object(b.jsx)(y.a.Item,{href:"/computersquiz/msword",className:"link",children:"MS Powerpoint"}),Object(b.jsx)(y.a.Item,{href:"/computersquiz/msword",className:"link",children:"MS Access"}),Object(b.jsx)(y.a.Item,{href:"/computersquiz/msword",className:"link",children:"Computer Networking"}),Object(b.jsx)(y.a.Item,{href:"/computersquiz/msword",className:"link",children:"DataBase"}),Object(b.jsx)(y.a.Item,{href:"/computersquiz/msword",className:"link",children:"Computer Fundamental"}),Object(b.jsx)(y.a.Item,{href:"/computersquiz/msword",className:"link",children:"MS Access"}),Object(b.jsx)(y.a.Divider,{}),Object(b.jsx)(y.a.Item,{href:"#action5",children:"Something else here"})]}),Object(b.jsx)(O.a.Link,{href:"#",disabled:!0,children:"Link"})]}),Object(b.jsxs)(x.a,{className:"d-flex",children:[Object(b.jsx)(x.a.Control,{type:"search",placeholder:"Search",className:"me-2","aria-label":"Search"}),Object(b.jsx)(f.a,{variant:"outline-success",children:"Search"})]})]})]})})},v=function(t){Object(h.a)(o,t);var e=Object(u.a)(o);function o(){return Object(d.a)(this,o),e.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(l.a)(o,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(b.jsx)("div",{children:Object(b.jsx)(q,{})})}}]),o}(n.Component),A=v;function S(){return Object(b.jsx)(c.a,{children:Object(b.jsx)(p.c,{children:Object(b.jsxs)(p.a,{path:"/",component:k,children:[Object(b.jsx)(p.a,{path:"/computersquiz/msword",element:Object(b.jsx)(j,{})}),Object(b.jsx)(p.a,{path:"/computersquiz",element:Object(b.jsx)(A,{})})]})})})}var k=function(){return Object(b.jsx)("div",{className:"App",children:Object(b.jsx)(S,{})})};s.a.render(Object(b.jsx)(i.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(b.jsx)(k,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[82,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.2472f028.chunk.js.map